<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DE_1</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">WELCOME TO</string>
    <string name="furniture">FURNITURE</string>
    <string name="new_york">The City of New York, usually called either New York City (NYC) or simply New York (NY), is the most populous city in the United States.
                            \nWith an estimated 2018 population of 8,398,748 distributed over a land area of about 302.6 square miles (784 km2), New York is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area,the largest metropolitan area in the world by urban landmass and one of the world s most populous megacities, with an estimated 19,979,477 people in its 2018 Metropolitan Statistical Area and 22,679,948 residents in its Combined Statistical Area.
                            \nA global power city, New York City has been described as the cultural, financial, and media capital of the world,and exerts a significant impact upon commerce, entertainment, research, technology, education, politics, tourism, art, fashion, and sports.
                            \nThe city\'s fast pace has inspired the term New York minute. Home to the headquarters of the United Nations, New York is an important center for international diplomacy.</string>
    <string name="iceland">Dublin (/ˈdʌblɪn/, locally /ˈdʊb-/; Irish: Baile Átha Cliath[12] [ˈbˠalʲə aːhə ˈclʲiə; ˌbʲlʲaː ˈclʲiə]) is the capital and largest city of Ireland.
                            \nSituated on a bay on the east coast, at the mouth of the River Liffey, it lies within the province of Leinster. It is bordered on the south by the Dublin Mountains, a part of the Wicklow Mountains range.
                            \nIt has an urban area population of 1,173,179,[8] while the population of the Dublin Region (formerly County Dublin) as of 2016 was 1,347,359.[7] The population of the Greater Dublin Area was 1,904,806 per the 2016 census.[15]  There is archaeological debate regarding precisely where Dublin was established by the Gaels in or before the 7th century AD.[16] Later expanded as a Viking settlement, the Kingdom of Dublin, the city became Ireland\'s principal settlement following the Norman invasion.
                            \nThe city expanded rapidly from the 17th century and was briefly the second largest city in the British Empire before the Acts of Union in 1800. Following the partition of Ireland in 1922, Dublin became the capital of the Irish Free State, later renamed Ireland.  Dublin is a historical and contemporary centre for education, the arts, administration and industry. As of 2018 the city was listed by the Globalization and World Cities Research Network (GaWC) as a global city, with a ranking of \"Alpha −\", which places it amongst the top thirty cities in the world.[17][18]</string>
    <string name="london">London is the capital and largest city of England and the United Kingdom, with the largest municipal population in the European Union.[7][8] Standing on the River Thames in the south-east of England, at the head of its 50-mile (80 km) estuary leading to the North Sea, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. Londinium was founded by the Romans.
                            \nThe City of London, London\'s ancient core − an area of just 1.12 square miles (2.9 km2) and colloquially known as the Square Mile − retains boundaries that follow closely its medieval limits. The City of Westminster is also an Inner London borough holding city status. Greater London is governed by the Mayor of London and the London Assembly.
                            \nLondon is considered to be one of the world\'s most important global cities[17][18][19] and has been termed the world\'s most powerful,[20] most desirable,[21] most influential,[22] most visited,[23] most expensive,[24][25] innovative,[26] sustainable,[27] most investment friendly,[28] most popular for work,[29] and the most vegetarian-friendly[30] city in the world. London exerts a considerable impact upon the arts, commerce, education, entertainment, fashion, finance, healthcare, media, professional services, research and development, tourism and transportation.[31][32] London ranks 26 out of 300 major cities for economic performance.[33] It is one of the largest financial centres[34] and has either the fifth or sixth largest metropolitan area GDP.[note 3][35][36][37][38][39] It is the most-visited city as measured by international arrivals[40] and has the busiest city airport system as measured by passenger traffic.[41] It is the leading investment destination,[42][43][44][45] hosting more international retailers[46][47] and ultra high-net-worth individuals[48][49] than any other city. London\'s universities form the largest concentration of higher education institutes in Europe.[50] In 2012, London became the first city to have hosted three modern Summer Olympic Games.[51]</string>
    <string name="paris">Paris (French pronunciation: ​[paʁi] (About this soundlisten)) is the capital and most populous city of France, with an area of 105 square kilometres (41 square miles) and an official estimated population of 2,140,526 residents as of 1 January 2019.
                            \nSince the 17th century, Paris has been one of Europe\'s major centres of finance, diplomacy, commerce, fashion, science, and the arts. The City of Paris is the centre and seat of government of the Île-de-France, or Paris Region, which has an estimated official 2019 population of 12,213,364, or about 18 percent of the population of France.[1] The Paris Region had a GDP of €709 billion ($808 billion) in 2017.[3] According to the Economist Intelligence Unit Worldwide Cost of Living Survey in 2018, Paris was the second most expensive city in the world, after Singapore, and ahead of Zürich, Hong Kong, Oslo and Geneva.
                            \nAnother source ranked Paris as most expensive, on a par with Singapore and Hong Kong, in 2018.[5]  The city is a major railway, highway, and air-transport hub served by two international airports: Paris-Charles de Gaulle (the second busiest airport in Europe) and Paris-Orly.[6][7] Opened in 1900, the city\'s subway system, the Paris Métro, serves 5.23 million passengers daily,[8] and is the second busiest metro system in Europe after Moscow Metro. Gare du Nord is the 24th busiest railway station in the world, but the first located outside Japan, with 262 million passengers in 2015.[9]  Paris is especially known for its museums and architectural landmarks: the Louvre was the most visited art museum in the world in 2018, with 10.2 million visitors.[10][11] The Musée d\'Orsay, Musée Marmottan Monet, and Musée de l\'Orangerie are noted for their collections of French Impressionist art, the Pompidou Centre Musée National d\'Art Moderne has the largest collection of modern and contemporary art in Europe, and the Musée Rodin and Musée Picasso exhibit the works of the two noted Parisians. The historical district along the Seine in the city centre is classified as a UNESCO Heritage Site, and popular landmarks in the city centre include the Cathedral of Notre Dame de Paris and the Gothic royal chapel of Sainte-Chapelle, both on the Île de la Cité; the Eiffel Tower, constructed for the Paris Universal Exposition of 1889; the Grand Palais and Petit Palais, built for the Paris Universal Exposition of 1900; the Arc de Triomphe on the Champs-Élysées, and the Basilica of Sacré-Coeur on the hill of Montmartre.</string>
    <string name="roma">Italy (Italian: Italia [iˈtaːlja] (About this soundlisten)), officially the Italian Republic (Italian: Repubblica Italiana [reˈpubblika itaˈljaːna]),[10][11][12][13] is a European country[a] consisting of a peninsula delimited by the Alps and surrounded by several islands.
                            \nLocated in the middle of the Mediterranean sea and traversed along its length by the Apennines, Italy has a largely temperate seasonal and Mediterranean climate. The country covers a total area of 301,340 km2 (116,350 sq mi), and land area of 294,140 km2 (113,570 sq mi), and shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, and the enclaved microstates of Vatican City and San Marino.
                            \nItaly has a territorial exclave in Switzerland (Campione) and a maritime exclave in the Tunisian Sea (Lampedusa). With around 60 million inhabitants, Italy is the fourth-most populous member state of the European Union.  Due to its central geographic location in Southern Europe and the Mediterranean, Italy has historically been home to myriad peoples and cultures. In addition to the various ancient peoples dispersed throughout modern-day Italy, the most predominant being the Indo-European Italic peoples who gave the peninsula its name, beginning from the classical era, Phoenicians and Carthaginians founded colonies mostly in insular Italy,[14] Greeks established settlements in the so-called Magna Graecia of Southern Italy, while Etruscans and Celts inhabited central and northern Italy respectively. An Italic tribe known as the Latins formed the Roman Kingdom in the 8th century BC, which eventually became a republic with a government of the Senate and the People. The Roman Republic initially conquered and assimilated its neighbours on the peninsula, eventually expanding and conquering parts of Europe, North Africa and Asia. By the first century BC, the Roman Empire emerged as the dominant power in the Mediterranean Basin and became the leading cultural, political and religious centre of Western civilisation, inaugurating the Pax Romana, a period of more than 200 years during which Italy\'s law, technology, economy, art, and literature developed.[15][16] Italy remained the homeland of the Romans and the metropole of the empire, whose legacy can also be observed in the global distribution of culture, governments, Christianity and the Latin script.</string>
    <string name="madrid">Madrid (/məˈdrɪd/, Spanish: [maˈðɾið])[n. 1] is the capital and most populous city of Spain. The city has almost 3.3 million[8] inhabitants and a metropolitan area population of approximately 6.5 million. It is the third-largest city in the European Union (EU), surpassed only by London and Berlin, and its monocentric metropolitan area is the third-largest in the EU, smaller only than those of London and Paris.
                            \nThe municipality covers 604.3 km2 (233.3 sq mi).[12]  Madrid lies on the River Manzanares in the centre of both the country and the Community of Madrid (which comprises the city of Madrid, its conurbation and extended suburbs and villages); this community is bordered by the autonomous communities of Castile and León and Castile-La Mancha. As the capital city of Spain, seat of government, and residence of the Spanish monarch, Madrid is also the political, economic and cultural centre of the country.
                            \nThe current mayor is José Luis Martínez-Almeida from the People\'s Party.  The Madrid urban agglomeration has the third-largest GDP[14] in the European Union and its influence in politics, education, entertainment, environment, media, fashion, science, culture, and the arts all contribute to its status as one of the world\'s major global cities.[15][16] Madrid is home to two world-famous football clubs, Real Madrid and Atlético Madrid. Due to its economic output, high standard of living, and market size, Madrid is considered the leading economic hub of the Iberian Peninsula and of Southern Europe.[17][18] It hosts the head offices of the vast majority of major Spanish companies, such as Telefónica, IAG or Repsol. Madrid is also the 10th most liveable city in the world according to Monocle magazine, in its 2017 index.[19]  Madrid houses the headquarters of the UN\'s World Tourism Organization (UNWTO), the Ibero-American General Secretariat (SEGIB), the Organization of Ibero-American States (OEI), and the Public Interest Oversight Board (PIOB). It also hosts major international regulators and promoters of the Spanish language: the Standing Committee of the Association of Spanish Language Academies, headquarters of the Royal Spanish Academy (RAE), the Cervantes Institute and the Foundation of Urgent Spanish (Fundéu BBVA). Madrid organises fairs such as FITUR,[20] ARCO,[21] SIMO TCI[22] and the Madrid Fashion Week.[23]</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
